A Guide to the Records of the Virginia Office of the Secretary of Natural Resources, 1992-2006 (bulk 2002-2005)
Library of Virginia
- Series III. Correspondence and Supporting Documents, Agencies, 1992-2006., Extent: 19 cu. ft. (Box 5-58.)
  - Chesapeake Bay Commission, 1994-2005. (Box 6-11.)
    - Survey of Chesapeake Bay Watershed Residents (Final Report), 2002-2003. (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - Survey of Chesapeake Bay Watershed Residents (Final Report), 2002-2003. (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - Survey of Chesapeake Bay Watershed Residents (Final Report), 2002-2003. (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Survey of Chesapeake Bay Watershed Residents (Final Report), 2002-2003. (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Chesapeake Bay Local Assistance Department, 2001-2005. (Box 11-13.)
    The Chesapeake Bay Local Assistance Department (CBLAD) was originally a separate entity, overseen by the Secretary of Natural Resources. As of July 1, 2004, CBLAD was merged into the Department of Conservation and Recreation (DCR). Within DCR, it became known as the Division of Chesapeake Bay Local Assistance. Its main purpose is to assist Virginia localities by studying current ordinances and making recommendations to bring them into accordance with the requirements set forth by the Chesapeake 2000 Agreement and the Chesapeake Preservation Act.
    Contains general office files and working papers compiled by the Office of the Secretary of Natural Resources with regard to the Chesapeake Bay Local Assistance Department. Despite the subtle name change that occurred after the merger with the Department of Recreation and Conservation, the Secretary's office staff continued to refer to it by its original name. Most of the CBLAD files contain general correspondence and administrative information about the division and its work with the Chesapeake Bay Program and the Chesapeake Bay Preservation Act.
    - Administrative, 2002-2003. (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Administrative, 2003-2004. (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Administrative, 2004. (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Administrative, 2004. (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Director, 2003. (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Executive Agreement, 2002. (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - General, 2001. (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - General, 2002. (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - General, 2002. (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - General, 2002. (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - General, 2003. (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - General, 2003. (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - General, 2004. (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - General, 2004. (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - General, 2004. (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - General, 2005. (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Local Ordinance Amendments, 2003. (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Working File, 2003. (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Working File, 2003. (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Working File, 2003. (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Working File, 2003. (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Working File, 2003. (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Working File, 2003. (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Working File, 2003. (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Working File, 2003. (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Working File, 2003. (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - Working File, 2003. (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Working File, 2003. (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - Working File, 2003. (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - Working File, 2003. (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Conservation and Recreation, Department of, 1998-2006. (Box 13-24.)
    The goals of the Virginia Department of Conservation and Recreation (DCR) are to conserve, protect, enhance, and advocate the wise use of the Commonwealth's unique natural, historic, recreational, scenic and cultural resources. The agency operates 34 state parks, manages more than 45 natural areas, facilitates statewide programs to reduce water pollution, regulates dams, helps with land conservation efforts and inventories rare and endangered plants, animals and their habitats.
    This subseries contains correspondence, meeting material, and other working papers compiled by the Office of the Secretary of Natural Resources with regard to the activities of the Department of Conservation and Recreation. Notable material includes Virginia Land Conservation Foundation Board meeting records, files pertaining to the Invasive Species Council, as well as files devoted to various issues involving Virginia's State Parks. Additional records pertaining to the Secretary's involvement with the Chesapeake Bay Commission can be found in Subseries A. Chesapeake Bay Commission. It is unknown why these records were filed in two places by the office staff, and as a result there may be some overlap. Researchers should utilize the records of both subseries.
    - Administrative, 2001-2002. (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Administrative, 2002-2003. (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Administrative, 2003-2006. (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Chesapeake Bay Commission, 2002-2005. (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Chesapeake Bay Commission--Chesapeake Executive Council Meeting, 2005 November. (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Chesapeake Bay Commission--Chesapeake Executive Council Meeting, 2005 November. (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Chesapeake Bay Commission Meeting, 2001 September. (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Chesapeake Bay Commission Meeting, 2001 December. (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Chesapeake Bay Commission Meetings, 2002 January and September. (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - Chesapeake Bay Commission Meeting, 2002 November. (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Chesapeake Bay Commission Meeting, 2002 November. (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - Chesapeake Bay Commission Meeting, 2003 May. (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - Chesapeake Bay Commission Meeting, 2003 May. (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - Chesapeake Bay Commission Meeting, 2003 November. (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - Chesapeake Bay Commission Meeting, 2003 November. (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - Chesapeake Bay Commission Meeting, 2004 January. (Box 13, Folder 17)
    - Chesapeake Bay Commission Meeting, 2004 January. (Box 13, Folder 18)
    - Chesapeake Bay Commission Meeting, 2004 May. (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Chesapeake Bay Commission Meeting, 2004 May. (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Chesapeake Bay Commission Meeting, 2004 November. (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Chesapeake Bay Commission Meeting, 2004 November. (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Chesapeake Bay Commission Meeting, 2005 September. (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Chesapeake Bay Commission Meeting, 2005 November. (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Chesapeake Bay Commission Meeting, 2005 November. (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Chesapeake Bay Commission Meeting, 2005 November. (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Chesapeake Bay Commission Meeting, 2006 January. (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Chesapeake Bay Commission Meeting, 2006 January. (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - Chesapeake Bay Commission--Principals' Staff Committee, 2001-2002. (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - Chesapeake Bay Commission--Principals' Staff Committee, 2003. (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - Chesapeake Bay Commission--Principals' Staff Committee, 2003. (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - Chesapeake Bay Commission--Virginia Delegation Meeting, 2002. (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - Chesapeake Bay Restoration Fund, 1998-2006. (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - Chippokes Plantation Farm Foundation, 1999. (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Chippokes Plantation Farm Foundation, 2002-2004. (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Clean Water Action Plan (Water Quality Initiatives), 2002-2003. (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Conservation Reserve Enhancement Program (CREP), 1999-2000. (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Conservation Reserve Enhancement Program (CREP), 2001. (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Conservation Reserve Enhancement Program (CREP), 2002-2003. (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Conservation Reserve Enhancement Program (CREP), 2004. (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Eppington Foundation, 2003. (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Executive Agreement, 2002-2005. (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Explore Park, 2003. (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - Explore Park, 2003. (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - Explore Park, 2003-2005. (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - Fall River Renaissance, 2002. (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - Federal Farm Bill, 2002. (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - Federal Farm Bill, 2002. (Box 15, Folder 15)
    - Federal Farm Bill, 2002. (Box 15, Folder 16)
    - Federal Farm Bill (2007), 2005. (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Federal Farm Bill (2007), 2005. (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - General Correspondence, 2002. (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - General Correspondence, 2002. (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - General Correspondence, 2002. (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - General Correspondence, 2002. (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - General Correspondence, 2003. (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - General Correspondence, 2003. (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - General Correspondence, 2003. (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - General Correspondence, 2003. (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - General Correspondence, 2003. (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - General Correspondence, 2004. (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - General Correspondence, 2004. (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - General Correspondence, 2004. (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - General Correspondence, 2004. (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - General Correspondence, 2004. (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - General Correspondence, 2004. (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - General Correspondence, 2004. (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - General Correspondence, 2004. (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - General Correspondence, 2005. (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - General Correspondence, 2005. (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - General Correspondence, 2005. (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - General Correspondence, 2005. (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - General Correspondence, 2005. (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - General Correspondence, 2005. (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - General Correspondence, 2005. (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - General Correspondence, 2005. (Box 17, Folder 14)
    - General Correspondence, 2005. (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Gun Ban (State Parks), 2002. (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Gun Ban (State Parks), 2002. (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Gun Ban (State Parks), 2002. (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Indian Burial Site and Memorial, 2001-2002. (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Invasive Species Council, 2002. (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Invasive Species Council, 2003. (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Invasive Species Council, 2003. (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Invasive Species Council, 2003. (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Invasive Species Council, 2003. (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Invasive Species Council, 2004. (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - Invasive Species Council, 2004. (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - Invasive Species Council, 2004. (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - Invasive Species Council, 2004. (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - Invasive Species Council, 2005. (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - Invasive Species Council, 2005. (Box 18, Folder 16)
    - Land Conservation Funding, 2002-2003. (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - National Water Trail (Captain John Smith), 2003-2005. (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - National Water Trail (Captain John Smith), 2005. (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Natural Heritage Program, 2002-2003. (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Natural Resources Leadership Council of the States, 2002-2003. (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - New River Land Trust, 2002-2003. (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Occoneechee State Park (SB 249), 2002. (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Occoneechee State Park (SB 249), 2002. (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - Occoneechee State Park (SB 249), 2002. (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - Occoneechee State Park (SB 249), 2002-2003. (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - Occoneechee State Park (SB 249), 2003. (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - Occoneechee State Park (SB 249), 2003-2004. (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - Occoneechee State Park (SB 249), 2004-2005. (Box 19, Folder 13)
    - Operation Spruce-Up, 2001-2002. (Box 19, Folder 14)
    - Poultry Industry, 2000-2002. (Box 19, Folder 15)
    - Regulations, 2001-2003. (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Resource Conservation and Development Councils, 2002-2003. (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Soil and Water Conservation, 2001-2002. (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Soil and Water Conservation, 2002. (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Soil and Water Conservation, 2002-2003. (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Soil and Water Conservation, 2003-2005. (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - State Parks, 2002. (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - State Parks, 2002. (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - State Parks, 2002. (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - State Parks, 2002. (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - State Parks, 2002. (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - State Parks, 2003. (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - State Parks, 2003. (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - State Parks, 2003. (Box 20, Folder 14)
    - State Parks, 2005. (Box 20, Folder 15)
    - Stewardship Virginia, 2003-2005. (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Stormwater Management, 2002-2003. (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Stormwater Management, 2003-2004. (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Stormwater Management, 2004-2005. (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Trails, 1999-2003. (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Virginia Land Conservation Foundation Board Manual, 2005. (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Virginia Land Conservation Foundation Board Manual, 2005. (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Virginia Land Conservation Foundation Board Manual, 2005. (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Virginia Land Conservation Foundation Board Manual, 2005. (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - Virginia Land Conservation Foundation Board Meeting Materials, 2004 November. (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - Virginia Land Conservation Foundation Board Meeting Materials, 2004 November. (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - Virginia Land Conservation Foundation Board Meeting Materials, 2004 November. (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - Virginia Land Conservation Foundation Board Meeting Materials, 2004 November. (Box 21, Folder 13)
    - Virginia Land Conservation Foundation Board Meeting Materials, 2005 June. (Box 21, Folder 14)
    - Virginia Land Conservation Foundation Board Meeting Materials, 2005 June. (Box 21, Folder 15)
    - Virginia Land Conservation Foundation Board Meeting Materials, 2005 June. (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Virginia Land Conservation Foundation Board Meeting Materials, 2005 June. (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Virginia Land Conservation Foundation Board Meeting Materials, 2005 December. (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Virginia Land Conservation Foundation Board Meeting Materials (misc.), 2005. (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - Virginia Land Conservation Foundation Board Meeting Materials (misc.), 2005. (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Virginia Land Conservation Foundation Board Meeting Materials (misc.), 2005. (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - Virginia Land Conservation Foundation Board Meeting Materials (misc.), 2005. (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - Virginia Land Conservation Foundation Correspondence, 1999-2001. (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - Virginia Land Conservation Foundation Correspondence, 2001-2002. (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - Virginia Land Conservation Foundation Correspondence, 2002-2004. (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - Virginia Land Conservation Foundation Correspondence, 2004-2005. (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - Virginia Land Conservation Foundation Correspondence, 2005. (Box 22, Folder 12)
    - Virginia Land Conservation Foundation Correspondence, 2005-2006. (Box 22, Folder 13)
    - Virginia Outdoors Foundation, 2001-2002. (Box 22, Folder 14)
    - Virginia Outdoors Foundation, 2002-2003. (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Virginia Outdoors Foundation, 2004-2006. (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Virginia Outdoors Foundation--Aldie Mill Issues, 1998-2002. (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Virginia Outdoors Foundation--Aldie Mill Issues, 1998-2002. (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Virginia Outdoors Foundation--Aldie Mill Issues, 1998-2002. (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Virginia Outdoors Foundation--Aldie Mill Issues, 1998-2002. (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Virginia Outdoors Foundation--Aldie Mill Issues, 1998-2002. (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Virginia Outdoors Foundation--Aldie Mill Issues, 1998-2002. (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - Virginia Outdoors Foundation--Aldie Mill Issues, 1998-2002. (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Virginia Outdoors Foundation--Wintergreen Conservation Easement, 2005. (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - Water Resources Development Act (WRDA), 2002. (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - Water Quality Improvement Fund, 2001-2002. (Box 23, Folder 12)
    - Watershed Protection Initiative, 2002-2003. (Box 23, Folder 13)
    - Widewater Peninsula Property, 1998. (Box 23, Folder 14)
    - Widewater Peninsula Property, 2002. (Box 23, Folder 15)
    - Widewater Peninsula Property, 2003. (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Widewater Peninsula Property, 2003. (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Widewater Peninsula Property, 2003. (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Widewater Peninsula Property, 2003. (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - Widewater Peninsula Property, 2003. (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - Widewater Peninsula Property, 2004. (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Council on Indians, Virginia, 2004-2005. (Box 24.)
    The Virginia Council on Indians (VCI) serves as an advisory board to the Governor and the General Assembly. The Council's duties include studying and researching the Indian Tribes in the Commonwealth, and making recommendations to the state on issues affecting Virginia Indians.
    This subseries contains correspondence and subject files. Most of the files contain general information on the Council, its budget and programs. The folders labeled "Memorial" contain this same type of information as well as a limited amount of information on a proposed Indian memorial (2005).
    - General Correspondence, 2004. (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - General Correspondence, 2004-2005. (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - Memorial, 2004. (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - Memorial, 2004. (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - Memorial, 2005. (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - Memorial, 2005. (Box 24, Folder 12)
    - Virginia Indian Heritage Program, 2004-2005. (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Environmental Quality, Department of, 1992-2006. (Box 24-47.)
    The Virginia Department of Environmental Quality (DEQ) administers state and federal laws and regulations for air quality, water quality, water supply and waste management. The DEQ is responsible for issuing permits, conducting inspections, and enforcing environmental regulations. The agency promotes recycling and the prevention of pollution and litter, protects Virginia's coastal areas, and is responsible for reviewing the environmental impacts of state and federal projects.
    This subseries contains correspondence, reports and other working papers pertaining to the activities of the Department of Environmental Quality. Notable topics include relations with the U.S. Environmental Protection Agency (EPA), landfill projects, the "Ghost Fleet" of decommissioned ships anchored in the Tidewater area, the 2002 drought and the King William Reservoir Project, and the department's yearly Environmental Stewardship Awards given to individuals and organizations involved in environmental awareness projects. Also included are general correspondence files and other administrative records. A majority of the DEQ records were divided up into the following categories: Air, Special, Waste Management, and Water. The files were alphabetically maintained in this order. Other files that were not included in a specific category can be found in alphabetical order after the categorized records.
    - Air
      - Air Quality and Transportation Issues (Northern Virginia), 2003. (Box 24, Folder 14)
      - Air Quality and Transportation Issues (Northern Virginia), 2003. (Box 24, Folder 15)
      - Air Quality and Transportation Issues (Northern Virginia), 2004. (Box 24, Folder 16)
      - Air Quality and Transportation Issues (Northern Virginia), 2004. (Box 25, Folder 1)
      - Air Quality and Transportation Issues (Northern Virginia), 2004-2005. (Box 25, Folder 2)
      - Chicago Climate Exchange (CCX), 2003. (Box 25, Folder 3)
      - Chicago Climate Exchange (CCX), 2004. (Box 25, Folder 4)
      - Chicago Climate Exchange (CCX), 2004-2005. (Box 25, Folder 5)
      - Dominion Virginia Power, 2002-2003. (Box 25, Folder 6)
      - Dominion Virginia Power, 2002-2003. (Box 25, Folder 7)
      - Environmental Protection Agency (EPA), 2001-2003. (Box 25, Folder 8)
      - Environmental Protection Agency (EPA), 2003. (Box 25, Folder 9)
      - Environmental Protection Agency (EPA), 2004. (Box 25, Folder 10)
      - Environmental Protection Agency (EPA), 2004. (Box 25, Folder 11)
      - Environmental Protection Agency (EPA), 2004. (Box 25, Folder 12)
      - Environmental Protection Agency (EPA), 2004-2005. (Box 25, Folder 13)
      - Expedited Rulemaking, 2003. (Box 25, Folder 14)
      - Green Motor Lines, 2003. (Box 25, Folder 15)
      - Legal Challenges, 2002. (Box 25, Folder 16)
      - Mirant, 2003. (Box 25, Folder 17)
      - Mirant, 2003-2004. (Box 26, Folder 1)
      - Mirant, 2004-2005. (Box 26, Folder 2)
      - New Source Review (Clean Air Act), 2002. (Box 26, Folder 3)
      - New Source Review (Clean Air Act), 2002. (Box 26, Folder 4)
      - New Source Review (Clean Air Act), 2002-2003. (Box 26, Folder 5)
      - New Source Review (Clean Air Act), 2003-2005. (Box 26, Folder 6)
      - Nitrogen Oxide (Virginia State Implementation Plan), 2001-2002. (Box 26, Folder 7)
      - Nitrogen Oxide (Virginia State Implementation Plan), 2002-2004. (Box 26, Folder 8)
      - Ozone Non-Attainment, 2001. (Box 26, Folder 9)
      - Ozone Non-Attainment, 2002-2003. (Box 26, Folder 10)
      - Ozone Transport Commission, 1999-2002. (Box 26, Folder 11)
      - Ozone Transport Commission, 2002. (Box 26, Folder 12)
      - Toxic Release Inventory, 2002. (Box 26, Folder 13)
      - Toxic Release Inventory, 2003. (Box 26, Folder 14)
    - Special
      - Environmental Marketing, 2002. (Box 27, Folder 1)
      - Ghost Fleet (Clark v. MARAD), 2001-2002. (Box 27, Folder 2)
      - Ghost Fleet (Clark v. MARAD), 2002. (Box 27, Folder 3)
      - Ghost Fleet (Clark v. MARAD), 2002. (Box 27, Folder 4)
      - Ghost Fleet (Clark v. MARAD), 2002. (Box 27, Folder 5)
      - Ghost Fleet (Clark v. MARAD), 2002. (Box 27, Folder 6)
      - Ghost Fleet (Clark v. MARAD), 2002. (Box 27, Folder 7)
      - Ghost Fleet (Clark v. MARAD), 2002. (Box 27, Folder 8)
      - Ghost Fleet (Clark v. MARAD), 2002-2003. (Box 27, Folder 9)
      - Ghost Fleet (Clark v. MARAD), 2003. (Box 27, Folder 10)
      - Ghost Fleet (Clark v. MARAD), 2005. (Box 27, Folder 11)
    - Waste Management
      - Barge Regulations, 2003. (Box 27, Folder 12)
      - Barge Regulations, 2003. (Box 27, Folder 13)
      - Barge Regulations, 2003. (Box 27, Folder 14)
      - Barge Regulations, 2003. (Box 27, Folder 15)
      - Barge Regulations, 2003. (Box 28, Folder 1)
      - Campaign Virginia (Interstate Transportation of Waste), 1998. (Box 28, Folder 2)
      - Campaign Virginia (Interstate Transportation of Waste), 1999. (Box 28, Folder 3)
      - Campaign Virginia (Interstate Transportation of Waste), 2000. (Box 28, Folder 4)
      - Campaign Virginia (Interstate Transportation of Waste), 2000. (Box 28, Folder 5)
      - Campaign Virginia (Interstate Transportation of Waste), 2000-2001. (Box 28, Folder 6)
      - Campaign Virginia (Interstate Transportation of Waste), 2001. (Box 28, Folder 7)
      - Campaign Virginia (Interstate Transportation of Waste), 2001. (Box 28, Folder 8)
      - Campaign Virginia (Interstate Transportation of Waste), 2001. (Box 28, Folder 9)
      - Campaign Virginia (Interstate Transportation of Waste), 2004. (Box 28, Folder 10)
      - Electronic Waste Issues, 2004-2005. (Box 28, Folder 11)
      - General Shale Company Expansion, 2002. (Box 28, Folder 12)
      - Hazardous Waste, 2002-2005. (Box 28, Folder 13)
      - Interstate Waste, 1997-2001. (Box 28, Folder 14)
      - Interstate Waste, 2001-2002. (Box 29, Folder 1)
      - Interstate Waste (Federal Legislation), 2002. (Box 29, Folder 2)
      - Interstate Waste (Federal Legislation), 2002. (Box 29, Folder 3)
      - Landfills, 2002. (Box 29, Folder 4)
      - Landfills, 2002. (Box 29, Folder 5)
      - Landfills, 2002-2003. (Box 29, Folder 6)
      - Landfills, 2003. (Box 29, Folder 7)
      - Landfills, 2003. (Box 29, Folder 8)
      - Landfills, 2003. (Box 29, Folder 9)
      - Landfills, 2003-2004. (Box 29, Folder 10)
      - Landfills, 2004. (Box 29, Folder 11)
      - Landfills, 2004. (Box 29, Folder 12)
      - Landfills, 2004. (Box 29, Folder 13)
      - Landfills, 2004. (Box 29, Folder 14)
      - Landfills, 2004. (Box 30, Folder 1)
      - Landfills, 2004. (Box 30, Folder 2)
      - Landfills, 2005. (Box 30, Folder 3)